‎这支萨尔萨乐曲献给亚伦萧
That salsa goes out to Aaron Shore,
‎-墨西哥人引以为豪的儿子 提名… ‎-等等 兄弟
-the proud son of Mexico nominated-- - Hold up, 'mano.
‎我从没在拉美派对上见过的人 ‎怎么突然就让墨西哥人引以为豪了
I've never seen him in the parranda, and suddenly he's a proud son of Mexico?
‎他从未站在墨西哥裔美国人…
-He's never stood with the Mexican-- -
‎抱歉 亲爱的 评论太糟了
Sorry, baby. That's shitty.
‎我还听过更糟的
I've heard worse.
‎别被这些话干扰
Just don't let it derail you.
‎-别动 ‎-什么意思
-Hold still. -What do you mean?
‎我的意思就是 别“米饭加豆子”了 ‎你长白发了吗
I'm just saying, don't rice-and-beans it. Are you going gray?
‎我就不假装听懂你的意思了 别弄了
I won't pretend I know what you're talking about. Stop it.
‎我们刚开始约会的时候 ‎你说你不喜欢米饭加豆子
When we first started dating, you said you didn't like rice and beans
‎因为大家都认为你会吃这种食物
'cause everyone expected you to eat that.
‎这根看上去花白了
This looks gray.
‎没有啊
No, it's not.
‎我给你做了我的私房米饭加豆子后 ‎你全吃完了
Then I made you my arroz con habichuela and you ate that shit up.
‎因为好吃啊 那你让我怎么办
It was good. What do you want me to do?
‎那是米饭加豆子啊
It was rice and beans.
‎好吧 你想说什么
Okay, what are you getting at?
‎不要因为担心被人套上刻板印象
Don't not do something good
‎就忌讳做一些好的事情
because you're worried about being stereotyped.
‎比如在本周的采访中推进移民改革
Like, say, pushing immigration reform at your interviews this week.
‎因为墨西哥人最关心的只有移民政策
Because all Mexicans want to talk about is immigration.
‎你很操心种族不平等问题啊 ‎波多黎各小姐
-That's very woke of you, Boricua. -
‎很好笑 老头子
Very funny, old man.
‎你为什么叫我“老头子” 老太婆
Who are you calling "old man," Granny?
‎你这个老头子
You, old man.
‎打扰了 总统先生 ‎您让我在情况变糟时来告知您
- Sorry, Mr. President. You told me to update you if things got worse?
‎没关系 拉塞尔 怎么了
It's all right, Russell. What's up?
‎俄亥俄州和宾夕法尼亚州的老师 ‎刚刚罢工了
Teachers in Ohio and Pennsylvania just went on strike.
‎罢工范围加起来有三个州的八个区
That makes eight districts in three states.
‎这也是欢迎孩子们返校的一种方式
Well, that's one way to welcome the kids back.
‎他们的诉求是什么
What are their demands?
‎课本和教学用品费 ‎以及工资上涨10%
Money for textbooks and supplies and a 10% salary increase.
‎谈判定在什么时候
When are negotiations set for?
‎双方都拒绝回到谈判桌
Both sides are refusing to come back to the table.
‎今天就这样开始了
And the day begins.
‎-让哈珀到椭圆形办公室见我 ‎-是 先生
-Have Harper meet me in the Oval. - Yes, sir.
‎这玩意真是难搞
These things are fucking impossible.
第三季   第四集
指定
幸存者
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
精校
压制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
‎我都要做噩梦了 梦到那个男人
I'm gonna have nightmares of that man
‎在白宫西厢追着我核对讲话要点
chasing me through the West Wing with talking points.
‎那你更应该好好塑造体型了
All the more reason to stay in shape.
‎-圆也是一种体型 ‎-你又不圆
-Round is a shape. -You're not round.
‎你觉得我应该给她准备点什么
So what do you think I should get her?
‎什么我以为她的生日 ‎已经过去好几个月了
What? I thought her birthday was months ago.
‎是 但我已经错过她那么多生日了 ‎上一个是21岁生日
Yeah, but I missed so many of them. And the last one was her 21st.
‎那就给她个烈酒杯
So, get her a shot glass.
‎这像是父亲送的礼物吗
Is that a fatherly gift?
‎哦 天啊 你想太多了 精子爸爸
Oh, my God. You're overthinking this, sperm daddy.
‎对了 副总统候选人亚伦萧 ‎在你的通讯资料集里
So, what's it like having vice-presidential candidate Aaron Shore
‎这种感觉如何
in your communications portfolio?
‎告诉他要做什么的感觉很有意思
Hmm. It's kinda fun telling him what to do,
‎但我说不好罗琳是在惩罚我 ‎还是开始信任我了
but I can't tell if Lorraine is punishing me or starting to trust me.
‎报道措词是你说了算 别忘了这一点
You control the narrative. Remember that.
‎在这方面 我们就是神明
We are as gods that way.
‎赛斯 首先 如果我有讲话要点
First off, Seth, if I have talking points,
‎我不会到处追你 应该是你来找我
I won't chase you down. You're coming to me.
‎第二 罗琳是在惩罚你 ‎她在惩罚我们所有人
Secondly, Lorraine is punishing you. She's punishing all of us.
‎第三 给那姑娘准备一份简单的礼物
And, thirdly, get the girl a simple gift.
‎-像袜子之类的 ‎-看看
-Like socks? - Oh, look.
‎好吧 更多老师罢工了
There we go. More teachers just walked out.
‎尊敬的神明要控制媒体措词
Your godliness needs to control the narrative.
‎我都跟你说了 是噩梦
I'm telling you, nightmares.
‎说到这个 你有没有打开
Speaking of, did you ever open that envelope
‎DNA癌症测试结果的信封
with the DNA cancer test results thingy?
‎我不想聊这个
I don't wanna talk about it.
‎-有什么进展要告诉我 好吗 ‎-好
- Just keep me posted, okay? -Yeah.
‎快点 磨蹭鬼
Come on, slowpoke.
‎-这些是什么 ‎-我妈寄来的一些照片
-Oh, what's all this? -Some pictures my mom sent.
‎罗琳说这些照片 ‎能让我看起来更平易近人
Lorraine said they'd make me look more relatable.
‎-我得把它们装起来 ‎-不
-I gotta take them in. -No.
‎得先让我看一看才行
Not before I get a chance to look at them.
‎-真可爱 ‎-天啊
-Cute. -God.
‎-快点 磨蹭鬼 ‎-嘿
-Come on, slowpoke. -Hey.
‎一周的谈判 该死
A week's negotiation, shot.
‎莫斯要求州长们制止罢工
Moss is calling for the governors to break the strikes.
‎封锁教师 请来没参加罢工的人…
Lock out teachers, bring in the scabs...
‎这个混蛋一副自己已经当选的做派
Son of a bitch is acting like he's already been elected.
‎大部分罢工州的州长都是共和党
Republicans control the governorships in most of the striking states.
‎他无疑是在用内阁成员的席位 ‎来换取他们的忠诚
No doubt he's dangling cabinet positions for their loyalty.
‎他说如果他是总统 ‎他会调集国民警卫队
He said he'd bring in the National Guard if he were president.
‎还好他不是 波特怎么说
Thank God he's not. What about Porter?
‎“你是一个会引起纷争的总统
"You're a divisive president
‎在你领导下的美国 ‎正在走教育下坡路”
presiding over the downfall of education in the United States."
‎他一个亿万富翁
So says the billionaire
‎给自己化工精炼厂工人的工资 ‎都不足果腹 这种话还真说得出口
whose chemical refinery workers are paid starvation wages.
‎看啊 又有四个地区罢工 ‎一共有12个了
Here we go. Four more districts have gone on strike. Total of 12.
‎诉求相同 工资和教学用品
Same demands. Living wage and school supplies.
‎工资和教学材料 ‎什么时候成了非分的诉求了
Living wage and school supplies. When did that become a radical demand?
‎当我们开始妖魔化工会 ‎而不是像波特那样的人的时候
When we started to demonize unions instead of people like Porter.
‎我需要正在处理罢工事件的 ‎所有州长的直接联络方式
I want direct lines to every governor who's got a strike on their hands.
‎-等您回来就会放在您桌上 ‎-谢谢
-It'll be on your desk when you get back. -Thank you.
‎他们出来了
They're coming out!
‎萧先生 您订婚的传言是真的吗
Mr. Shore, are rumors of your engagement true?
‎-您选好结婚日期了吗 ‎-什么
-You picked a date yet? - What?
‎她在这做什么
What's she doing here?
‎-你计划要辞职… ‎-不知道
-Are you planning to resign... - No idea.
‎…协助未婚夫竞选吗
...to help your fianc茅 on the campaign trail?
‎你说什么
-Excuse me? -
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎这是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
‎有人在Reddit上发帖说 ‎看见你昨晚求婚了
Someone posted on Reddit that they saw you propose last night.
‎CNBS新闻什么时候开始 ‎追踪在线论坛上的八卦了
Since when does CNBS follow rumors posted on online forums?
‎网络嘛 亲爱的 ‎我可预测不出什么会成为热点
It's the Internet, sweetie. I can't predict what rises to the top.
‎那你怎么知道要开车来救我们
How'd you know to come riding to our rescue, then?
‎亚伦 我喜欢她 她既聪明又冷酷
Oh, Aaron, I like her. She's smart and unrelenting.
‎好吧 八卦不是我搞出来的
Okay, I didn't start the rumor,
‎但我确保了几个重要的渠道会收到它
but I did ensure that it made it into a few select inboxes.
‎你为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
‎嘿 大家都喜欢爱情故事 ‎这是很好的宣传方式
Hey, everyone loves romance, and it's great publicity.
‎-罗琳… ‎-这倒提醒了我
- That reminds me.
‎我们的媒体团队在争论该如何称呼你
Our press team is arguing about what to call you.
‎-西裔墨西哥裔拉美裔 ‎-别叫“西裔”
-Hispanic? Chicano? Latino? -Don't use "Hispanic."
‎“拉丁裔”越来越流行 但…
Um, "Latinx" is on the rise, but--
‎我不喜欢贴标签 可以吗
I don't like labels, all right?
‎非要说的话 我是德州墨西哥裔
In any case, I'd be a Tejano.
‎我母亲的家族在德州诞生前 ‎就生活在那片土地上了
My mom's family's been in Texas since before it was Texas.
‎目前 我们的线索有 ‎佛罗里达的死亡鸟类
So far, we have dead birds in Florida,
‎剑桥被洗刷干净的DIY生物实验室
a DIY biolab scrubbed clean in Cambridge,
‎多伦多爆发的流感和一名失踪的护士
a flu outbreak in Toronto and a missing nurse.
‎联邦调查局还在调查化名
FBI's still running aliases.
‎是的 这是我们在 ‎佛罗里达死鸟身上发现的菌株
Yeah. This is the strain that we found in the dead birds in Florida,
‎而这是在多伦多发现的菌株
and this is the strain we found in Toronto.
‎它们种类不同 但都被改造过
They're different strains, but they've both been manipulated.
‎佛罗里达流感包含天花的基因序列
The Florida flu contains gene sequences from smallpox.
‎多伦多流感有我无法辨别的序列
The Toronto flu has sequences I can't identify.
‎有人在试验流感病毒菌株 ‎尝试哪种有效
Someone is messing with flu strains, seeing what sticks.
‎你下一步如何打算
So, what's your next move?
‎疾控中心在监控流感爆发 ‎而我需要确凿的证据
The CDC's monitoring the flu outbreak, but I need a smoking gun.
‎这个足够确凿吗
This smoking enough for you?
‎卫生部报告了一场流感爆发
Health Department reports on a flu outbreak.
‎-看看信头 ‎-坦帕
-Check out the letterhead. - Tampa?
‎-鸟 ‎-这次是人
-The birds. -This time, it's people.
‎自非常规会议以来 你上升了五个点
You're up five points since the unconvention.
‎不用客气
You're welcome, by the way.
‎做讲话的人是他
He's the one that gave the speech.
‎科罗拉多的情况看起来很不错
Colorado's looking really good.
‎亚伦也拉到了 ‎新墨西哥和内华达的支持
And Aaron has put New Mexico and Nevada into play.
‎亚伦还是德州之子
And Aaron is a son of Texas.
‎但我们需要让这幅图符合现状 ‎总统先生
Yeah, but we need this to reflect reality, Mr. President.
‎-我们下一项议程… ‎-我们能不能利用
-The next thing on our agenda-- - Can we use this recent bump
‎近期的增长优势 来应对教师罢工
to our advantage in dealing with these teachers' strikes?
‎你知道我不能参与 ‎美国政府的官方事务
You know I can't weigh in on official USG business.
‎你什么时候避讳这个了
When has that ever stopped you?
‎好吧
Fine.
‎教育不会激励投票人 ‎就表达一下支持 然后继续忙别的吧
Education doesn't motivate voters, so just say you support it and move on.
‎至于罢工 要采取行动 ‎让波特看上去像个伪君子
And as to the strike, do something that makes Porter look like a hypocrite,
‎让莫斯看上去像个无情的混蛋
and Moss look like an unfeeling asshole.
‎好了 我需要你批准广告预算
Okay, I need you to approve our advertising budget.
‎我告诉过你 这个问题上我有些想法
I told you I had some thoughts on that.
‎总统是个大忙人…
The president is a very busy man--
‎电视预算方面我们超支了
We're overspending on our TV budget.
‎-我们需要广告 ‎-听我把话说完
-We need ads. -Just give me a minute.
‎我们需要广告 ‎但已经没人看电视广告了
We need ads, but nobody's watching TV commercials anymore.
‎想要让投入产出比最大化
And since we need to get the biggest bang for our buck,
‎我们就应该砍掉电视预算 ‎将线上花销翻三倍
we should cut our TV budget and triple our online spending.
‎这主意其实不赖
That, actually, is not a bad idea.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎我和当蒂埃文斯聊了 就是那个 ‎策划“柯克曼听你说”视频的人
I've been speaking with Dontae Evans, the man behind the Kirkman Listens videos,
‎我们做了一个计划 他就在外面
and we've come up with a plan. He's right outside.
‎我知道他 让他进来
I know who he is. Bring him in.
‎当蒂 总统要和你聊聊
Dontae, the president would like to speak with you.
‎当蒂 幸会 你有什么想法
Dontae, nice to see you. What have you got?
‎我想给你拍一段热搜视频 先生 ‎向公众讲述您的故事
I want to do a viral video of you, sir. Tell the public your story.
‎公众知道我的故事
The public knows my story.
‎是 先生 但他们不了解您 ‎不了解工作背后的那个人
Yes, sir, but they don't know you. The man inside the job.
‎一旦他们了解了 ‎就不会想让其他人来接手这份工作
And once they do, they won't want anyone else to do it.
‎您想一想 先生 总统生活中的一天
Think about it, sir. A day in the life of the president.
‎我现在就可以开始拍
I can start filming right now.
‎好吧
Okay, okay.
‎推特 #非法副总统 进入热门 ‎点击观看更多视频
柯克曼的副总统
选了个西裔佬
‎该死
Shit.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎总统给我说了叙利亚项目的最新情况
POTUS updated me on the Syria project.
‎这是我做的时间表
Here's my timeline.
‎我已经和他确认好了一份时间表 ‎他没说吗
I already cleared a timeline with him. He didn't mention?
‎你和国务院 ‎以及国土安全局协调好了
Oh. So you coordinated with the State Department, DHS?
‎-对 ‎-商会呢
-Yeah. -Commerce?
‎还没有 怎么了
Not yet, why?
‎明天和土耳其代表团的会议 ‎你准备好了吗
Are you prepped for this meeting with the Turkish delegation tomorrow?
‎马斯 请坐
Mars, take a seat.
‎成为副总统候选人是件大事 ‎如果没有你
Okay, look, this VP nod is a big deal, and I wouldn't be here
‎接纳当初那个 ‎政治学专业的学生 鞭策他
if you hadn't taken a young poli-sci major and kicked his ass
‎让他拥有成熟政治头脑 ‎我就不会有今天 谢谢你
into the savvy political mind you see before you. So, thank you.
‎目前其实我不能带酒回家
I'm actually not bringing alcohol into the home right now.
‎-林刚刚完成康复治疗 ‎-该死
-Lynn just got back from rehab. -Shit.
‎对不起
I'm... I'm sorry.
‎-她怎么样了 ‎-她很好
-How's she doing? -She's fine.
‎你想谢我
You want to thank me?
‎那就让土耳其人同意和库尔德人谈话
Get the Turks to agree to talk with the Kurds.
‎明天都安排好了 我的代理人…
It's all set for tomorrow. My deputy--
‎你的代理人 ‎我以为你会负责这些谈判
Your deputy? I thought these were your negotiations.
‎我的竞选活动本周就开始了 ‎所以我安排…
My campaign rollout's this week, so I delegated--
‎有件事我们要说清楚 ‎你仍然是国家安全顾问
Let's get one thing straight. You are still national security advisor.
‎你和罗琳可以在你的业余时间 ‎搞副总统竞选肥皂剧
You and Lorraine can play telenovela VP on your own time.
‎这才是你最重要的事务 ‎不可以安排给别人
This is your top priority, not something you delegate.
‎明白了
Got it?
‎是 明白了
-Yeah, I got it. -
‎4点你要参加大学动力活动
You have the College Powered event at 4:00.
‎我会去的 除非谈判重启
I'll be there unless the negotiations start up again.
‎不 你要和一些 ‎富到流油的基金人士视频通话
No, you're getting face time with some obscenely rich foundation folk.
‎-我们不接受政治行动委员会的赞助 ‎-基金会不是政治行动委员会
-We're not taking PACs. -Foundations are not PACs.
‎政治黑金反而更好吗
Dark money is better?
‎这些富有的基金会的人会对他施压
These rich foundation folk are just going to pressure him
‎让他签发非公开法案
to sign their nondisclosure bill.
‎我会否决那个法案的 艾米丽
I'm vetoing that bill, Emily.
‎我们不是该专心处理教师罢工吗
Shouldn't we be focusing on the teachers' strike?
‎缺席一场你作为重要嘉宾受邀的
Ditching an educational fundraiser
‎教育筹资会 真的很不好
at which you're the guest of honor is just terrible optics.
‎再说一次 这是一场 ‎专为一个教育基金会组织的活动
Again, this is a very exclusive event for an educational foundation
‎到场的客人付重金 ‎求取一个和总统合影的机会
whose guests have paid big bucks for a photo op with the president.
‎也许你还能得到如何处理罢工的灵感
Maybe you'll get some ideas on how to handle the walkouts.
‎当然了 因为亿万富翁 ‎理解工薪阶层需要什么
Sure, because billionaires understand what the working people need.
‎我们能不能不要当着孩子的面吵架
Could we not fight in front of the kids?
‎你们俩都冷静一下 当蒂 继续拍
Calm down, you two. Dontae, keep rolling.
‎我会和他们分享总统的名气
I'll simply be sharing the celebrity of the presidency with them.
‎不介意的话 失陪一下
If you don't mind, excuse me.
‎黛安让坦帕卫生部 ‎帮我们安排了一个实验室
Dianne got the Tampa Health Department to set us up with a lab.
‎她会飞过来给我们做简报
She'll fly down to debrief us.
‎我还是觉得开车比较好 ‎飞机是疾病的温床
Still wish we could've driven. Planes are breeding grounds for disease.
‎你对末日疾病的执念挺非常不健康
This doomsday disease obsession you have can't be healthy.
‎我们有抗生素和疫苗
We do have antibiotics and vaccines.
‎一个咳嗽可以传播五十万病毒微粒
A single cough spreads half a million virus particles.
‎让一个咳嗽的人登上空气循环的飞机
Put a coughing person on a plane with recycled air,
‎飞机就成了孵化器
it becomes an incubator.
‎受感染的乘客 ‎也许会从旧金山飞到伦敦
Infected passengers fly from San Francisco to London, maybe.
‎在途中 他们还会传染 ‎飞往温哥华或者内罗毕的人
Along the way, they infect others who are flying to Vancouver or Nairobi.
‎很快 世界就在 ‎我们无法治愈的瘟疫的掌控之中
And soon, the world is gripped by a plague from which we'll never recover.
‎-返程我们租车走 ‎-谢谢
-We'll rent a car on the way back. -Thank you.
亚伦里维拉 六年级
‎罗琳 好久不见
Lorraine. It's been ages.
‎-我想为今早的事道歉 ‎-都过去了
I wanted to apologize for this morning. What's done is done.
‎我让竞选团队出面破解了谣言
I had the campaign reach out and squash the rumors.
‎-这是什么 ‎-一件外套
-What is this? -A coat.
‎可以变成睡袋
It converts into a sleeping bag.
‎我有个承授人在雇佣 ‎无家可归的女人们制作这个
I have a grantee that's employing homeless women to make them.
‎我们明天有媒体活动
And we have a press event tomorrow,
‎-所以你能否… ‎-有谁会来
-so if you'll excuse me-- -Who do you have coming?
‎目前我邀请了 ‎一家本地报纸和一些线上博主
Uh, so far, I have a local newspaper and some online bloggers.
‎很好
Oh. That's nice.
‎你想干什么 罗琳
What do you want, Lorraine?
‎等一下
Hang on.
‎-我是为你母亲的事而来 ‎-我母亲怎么了
-I'm here about your mother. -What about my mother?
‎她参与了黑豹党的波多黎各分支
Her involvement with the Puerto Rican wing of the Black Panthers.
‎青年主人组织他们是不相关的群体
The Young Lords?  They were a separate group.
‎但都参与过受争议的活动
Both involved in controversial activities.
‎是 他们都有免费早餐项目
Yeah, they both ran free breakfast programs.
‎还持枪
And carried guns.
‎对莫斯那伙人来说 ‎持枪棕色人种就是超可怕的恐怖分子
To the Moss crowd, brown people with guns equals scary, scary terrorists.
‎我妈妈帮他们组织免费社区活动
My mom helped them organize free community events.
‎她在教堂地下室做衣服 ‎教孩子们识字
She made clothes and taught kids to read out of a church basement.
‎那个教堂是在她的小团体 ‎冲击市政办公室后武装占取的
A church that her little group took by force after trashing city offices.
‎整件事不是那样的
That's not the whole story.
‎但人们只关心这个部分
That's the part people will care about.
‎谁谁会关心我只是亚伦的女朋友
Who? Who's going to care? I'm just Aaron's girlfriend.
‎不 你的身份关系到这次竞选
No, you are the campaign's girlfriend.
‎因为鳏夫柯克曼没有约会对象
And with widow Kirkman off the market,
‎到了秋季 ‎你会是全美受到最多关注的女人
you're gonna be one of the most scrutinized women in America come fall.
‎我没兴趣当个道具
I'm not interested in being a prop.
‎不 你搞反了
No, you got it backwards.
‎我可以确保你不会再被忽视
I can make sure you're never overlooked again.
‎只要我…
As long as I...
‎缓和一下你的活动家的风格 ‎不要让别人注意到你母亲的过去
Tone down your activist tendencies. Don't call attention to your mom's past.
‎你想让我谴责我的母亲
You want me to denounce my mother.
‎你明天的活动 这个东西…
Your event tomorrow, this thing...
‎你想不想让它登上全国所有媒体
How'd you like for that to be covered by every media outlet in the country?
‎我喜欢你 真的
I like you. I really do.
‎我知道你想做什么 跻身男人的世界
And I see what you're doing here, breaking into that boys' club.
‎我想帮你 ‎但只有你自己也想帮自己才行
I want to help you, but I can't unless you help yourself.
‎这个很棒
That's cool.
‎这是给亚伦的
An update on the meeting
‎关于与土耳其外交部长会晤的更新
with the Turkish foreign minister for Aaron.
‎-我会看的 ‎-我说了是给亚伦的
-I'll take a look. -I said for Aaron.
‎亚伦明天有安排了 我来顶替他
Aaron's booked tomorrow. I'm covering it.
‎你们两个上次交谈是什么时候
When did you two last speak?
‎他十分钟前跟我聊过 怎么了
He briefed me ten minutes ago. Why?
‎又有六个地区在罢工
Six more districts are striking.
‎总计15个州的18个地区 ‎几乎占全国范围的三分之一
That's 18 districts in 15 states, nearly a third of the country.
‎该展开魅力攻势了
It's time for a charm offensive.
‎叫媒体来 从老师的角度进行报道
Bring the press in, tell the teachers' side of the story.
‎我去负责白宫方面的发言
I'll man the bully pulpit.
‎-您的否决声明呢 ‎-在我桌上
-Your veto statements? -On my desk.
‎现在罢工是最优先事项
Right now, the strike is the priority.
‎-马斯 我时间不多 ‎-我长话短说
-Mars, I don't have a lot of time. -I'll be brief.
‎-亚伦 这是你的新特选人员吗 ‎-先生 这位是特洛伊贝探员
- Aaron, is this your new detail? -Sir, Agent Troy Baye.
‎-一定要保证他安然无恙 ‎-我会的 总统先生
-Don't let anything happen to him. -Will do, Mr. President.
‎我是跟萧先生说的 小伙子
I was talking to Mr. Shore, son.
‎不行
No.
‎我有点担心亚伦的工作量
I'm concerned about Aaron's bandwidth.
‎我想让他放下叙利亚的谈判
I'd like to take him off the Syria negotiations.
‎是我把项目给他的
I gave him the project.
‎如果他要转派职责给其他人…
If he's gonna delegate responsibilities--
‎由亚伦负责 我需要你帮我打电话
Aaron's in charge. I need you to help me man the phones,
‎让州长们别做蠢事
stop the governors from doing something stupid.
‎我们要让各地区让步
We need to get the districts to give ground.
‎你能把叙利亚的事放在一边 ‎先处理这个吗
Can you get your mind off of Syria long enough to do that?
‎是 长官
Aye, aye, captain.
‎请接俄亥俄州长
Can I have the governor of Ohio, please?
‎梅根 你真的想花接下来的六周时间
Megan, do you really want to spend the next six weeks
‎为投票决定涨工资的事辩白 ‎而眼睁睁看着孩子们没课本用
defending voting yourselves raises while students go without textbooks?
‎议长先生 抱歉 能稍等一下吗
Mr. Speaker, I'm sorry. Can you give me a second?
‎我要和我的新闻秘书说几句话
I need to talk to my press secretary.
‎一、二、三…
One, two, three...
‎我刚得到一份清单
I've just been given a list of everything
‎列明了你愿意在 ‎孩子们的教育支出之外支付的费用
that you've been willing to pay for aside from our children's education.
‎教师要同时做两三份工作才能糊口
Teachers are working two, three jobs just to stay afloat.
‎你让学生在教室里穿厚外套
You've got students wearing jackets in their classrooms
‎因为你拒绝修暖气 ‎你还担心我的公众形象
because you refuse to fix the heat, and you're worried about my optics?
‎归根结底还是公众的接受度
It's all about optics.
‎采访一些教师 要附上真人形象
Interview some teachers. Put a human face on it.
‎我可以给你接视频通话
I can get you face time.
‎我不在乎 做好你的工作 ‎让你的老师们回去上班
I don't give a damn. Do your job and get your teachers back to work.
‎算我欠你的
I'd owe you.
‎去你的
Screw that.
‎抱歉 当蒂 ‎没让你拍到什么精彩的东西
Sorry, Dontae. Not exactly riveting stuff.
‎这样很好 先生
It's fascinating, sir.
‎你对州长们有什么看法
So, what do you think about the governors?
‎我觉得他们很好 先生
I think they're fine, sir.
‎我自认为是个希望周围人
I like to think I'm someone who is comfortable
‎都能畅所欲言的人
surrounding himself with people who say what's on their mind.
‎他们都没抓住重点
It's just they're all missing the point.
‎他们说的都是狗屁陈词滥调 ‎哦 天啊…
They're giving bullshit platitudes. Oh, God--
‎没关系 我是总统 不是你祖母
It's fine. It's fine. I'm the president, not your grandmother.
‎我只是想说…
I just mean...
‎这些州长里有几个人 ‎在过去十年中去过公立学校
How many of these governors have been to a public school in the last ten years?
‎我的学校有书龄15年的老教科书 ‎被强力胶带绑在一起
My school had 15-year-old textbooks held together by duct tape.
‎我的老师们都是伟大的战士
And my teachers were warriors.
‎他们每天都奋力拼搏 ‎想给我们一个未来
They fought every day to give us a future.
‎是啊
Exactly.
‎我母亲是个历史老师
My mother was a history teacher.
‎她每天回家有山一样的报告要读 ‎好多试卷要批
She would come home with mounds of reports to read, tests to grade.
‎她班上有些孩子 家里穷得一无所有
Some of the kids in her class came from families with no money,
‎她就为他们做午餐 好让他们吃上饭
so she would make them lunches so they'd have something to eat.
‎有一次 我问她为什么这么做
I once asked her why she did all that.
‎她只是笑笑说 ‎“这是老师应该做的”
She just smiled and said, "That's what teachers do."
‎没有比老师更崇高的职业了
Ain't no more noble profession.
‎等等 您能再说一次吗
Wait, could you repeat that?
‎抱歉 我只有第一遍能说好
I'm sorry, I'm only good on the first take.
‎好吧 先生
All right, sir.
‎跟我说说您父亲吧
Tell me about your dad.
‎我父亲
My dad.
‎我父亲以前是个合同工
My father was a contractor.
赛斯怀特
‎赛斯的礼物提案第327号…
太做作了？
信封拆开了吗？
‎什么事
- -Yeah?
‎-罗琳想见你 ‎-好
-Lorraine wants to see you. -Right.
‎谢谢你 凯拉
Thanks, Kayla.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎你好 这是亚伦的数据 ‎他的喜爱度已经爆表
Hi. Aaron's numbers. His likability is through the roof.
‎很好 但我们有个麻烦
Good, but we have a problem.
‎亚伦的审查员 ‎发现了一些银行违规行为
Aaron's vetters have found some banking irregularities.
‎几年前持续付款给 ‎一个叫马里卢斯圣地亚哥的女人
Consistent payments a few years back to a woman named Mariluz Santiago.
‎我要你去确认 这些不是儿童抚养费
I need you to make sure they're not child support payments.
‎这不是审查员的工作吗
Isn't that what vetters are for?
‎我需要律师找不到的东西 ‎你了解他 上过他
I need the stuff that lawyers can't find. You know him. You fucked him.
‎-不 其实我没有 ‎-真的
-No, I didn't, actually. -Really?
‎你错过了这么好的机会
You let that get by you? Ouch.
‎-肯定后悔死了 ‎-罗琳…
-Gotta be a regret. -Lorraine--
‎但你还是有获取信息的渠道 ‎亲爱的 好好利用
But, still, you have access, darling. Use it.
‎我不会背叛亚伦的
I'm not gonna betray Aaron.
‎如果你不做好自己的工作 ‎让这桩丑闻面世
You'd be betraying him and your boss if you didn't do your job
‎才是背叛了他以及你的老板
and get in front of this scandal.
佛罗里达州 坦帕
金河谷出租公寓
‎好 我们从顶楼开始
All right, let's start at the top floor.
‎肖恩格林
Shawn Green?
‎你看起来不太舒服
You look a little under the weather there.
‎你出现这些症状有多久了
How long have you had these symptoms?
‎-你感觉不好有多久了 ‎-从妈妈生病开始
- And how long have you felt bad? -Since Mom got sick.
‎你妈妈也病了
-Your mommy's sick, too? -Mmm-hmm.
‎你最近有不寻常的访客吗
Have you had any unusual visitors lately?
‎除你以外没有
No one except you.
‎你好 萨凡先生 ‎我们是坦帕卫生服务中心的
Hi, Mr. Sa Pham? We're from the Tampa Health Services.
‎我们听说你最近病了
We heard you've been sick lately.
‎抱歉 你身体怎么样
- Uh... Sorry. How is your health?
‎就是有点发烧
Just a little fever.
‎多久了
How long?
‎可能一个星期吧
Maybe one week?
‎好
Okay.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎-谢谢 ‎-谢谢
- Thank you. -Thank you.
‎祝你早日康复
I hope you feel better.
‎你会说越南语
- -You speak Vietnamese?
‎一点吧 我以前和我妈会稍微说一些
I mean, barely. I spoke some with my mom.
‎现在不说了
Not anymore?
‎我爸不喜欢我们讲自己的悄悄话
Uh, my dad didn't like us having our own little thing.
‎他真的很混蛋
He was a real dick about it.
‎他不会说越南语吗
He didn't speak?
‎哦 不会 他是个安格鲁撒克逊白人
Oh, no. He's a WASP.
‎-怪不得 ‎-什么怪不得
-That explains it. -Explains what?
‎你和那个男人 ‎你们有不同特征 不同肤色
That man and you. You have different features, different skin.
‎他的黑色素比你的多
And his melanin pops in a way yours doesn't.
‎东南亚人 有的肤色浅 有的肤色深
Well, Southeast Asians, some are light and some are dark.
‎名单给我看一下
Give me that list.
‎等等 汉娜
Wait. Hannah.
‎你好 弗雷泽先生
Hello. Mr. Frazier?
‎约翰逊太太我们是坦帕卫生部的
Ms. Johnson? Tampa Health Department.
‎很抱歉打扰您 您感觉身体如何
We're sorry to interrupt your day, but how have you been feeling?
‎流感当然没有 亲爱的 ‎为什么这么问
The flu? Certainly not, dear. Why do you ask?
‎嘿 准备好回家了吗
Hey. Ready to head home?
‎是的 等我一下
Yeah, just give me a second.
‎好
Okay.
混蛋柯克曼选择定锚婴儿！
‎#非法副总统
又一个从真美国人手上偷走工作的
‎棕皮肤男孩#非法副总统
‎该死
Shit.
‎我们现在能走了吗
Could we get out of here already?
‎为了等你做完工作 ‎我都等过好几个小时了
I've spent hours of my life waiting for you to finish things up.
‎你也可以等我五分钟的
You can wait five minutes for me.
‎-这是什么 ‎-佩德罗阿尔毕祖坎伯斯
-What is this? -Pedro Albizu Campos.
‎波多黎各的自由战士
Puerto Rican freedom fighter?
‎美国关押他
The US imprisoned him
‎在他身上做核试验 直到他死去
and did nuclear experiments on him till he died.
‎那些是辐射灼伤
Those are radiation burns.
‎那一定是阴谋论
That's gotta be a conspiracy theory.
‎上网搜一下
Well, google that shit.
‎你熟悉叙利亚的地缘政治历史
How do you know the history of Syrian geopolitics
‎对土耳其、俄罗斯和伊朗也都很了解 ‎却不知道这件事
vis-脿-vis Turkey, Russia and Iran, and you don't know about this?
‎这不是我的历史 ‎我是墨西哥裔美国人
Because it's not my history. I'm Mexican American.
‎-真看不出来 ‎-什么
-You wouldn't know it. -Excuse me?
‎我真的得赶紧完成这个 ‎我们等会儿…
I really need to finish this. Can we talk--
‎我不把它摆到每个人面前
Just because I don't shove it in everyone's face,
‎不代表我的拉丁血脉就比你少
doesn't make me less Latino than you.
‎我没把什么东西摆到别人…什么
I don't shove anything in anyone... What?
‎那你这怎么全是这些东西
Then why would you have all this shit around, then?
‎因为我不会在这伪装自己
Because I'm not out here trying to pretend
‎-装出另一幅面孔 ‎-我也不会
-I'm something I'm not. -Neither am I.
‎好了 亚伦萧
Okay, Aaron Shore.
‎你慢慢来
Just take your time.
‎我们回去再谈…
-Can we just talk about this back at-- -
‎我喜欢
I love this.
‎什么乞求残羹剩饭吗
What? Begging for scraps?
‎不 追捕猎物
No, hunting my prey.
‎看看他们 就像装进桶里的鱼
Look at 'em. They're like fish in a barrel.
‎被免费香槟和小盘三文鱼 ‎骗得自鸣得意
Lulled into complacency by free champagne and tiny little plates of salmon.
‎真是让人兴奋
Ooh, it's so arousing.
‎放轻松 童子军 你会习惯的
Lighten up, Boy Scout. You'll get the hang of it.
‎来吧 加略特
-Ah. Here we go. Garrett. -Ah.
‎德特维尔先生 ‎您今晚主办的宴会非常棒
Mr. Detwiler. You've put together a lovely evening here.
‎总统先生 多谢光临
Mr. President, thank you for coming.
‎对您的基金表示祝贺 ‎您在做一些很伟大的事
Congratulations on your foundation. You've been doing some great things.
‎您找到全国成绩优异的学生
You found the top performers from across the country,
‎为他们支付大学学费
paying for their college educations.
‎我希望每个学生都能有此荣幸
I wish every student could have that advantage.
‎我是个社会达尔文主义者 ‎精华自然会浮在上层
I'm more of a social Darwinist. The cream rises to the top.
‎-失陪了 总统先生 ‎-好的
-Excuse me, Mr. President. -Of course.
‎他是在制药业赚到的钱
He made his money in pharma.
‎他过去也是莫斯的大捐助人 ‎在他的政府工作过
He also was a huge Moss donor and worked in his administration.
‎那为什么邀请我
Then why invite me?
‎利用一个人并不需要你喜欢他
You don't have to like someone to use them.
‎-谢谢 对 ‎-这就对了
-Thank you. Right. - There you go.
‎我们快点把这事做完
Let's get this over with.
‎-你好 ‎-你好
- Hi. -Hi.
‎看 这是她去打保龄球 度假…
Look, this is her bowling, on vacation...
‎高中毕业典礼
High school graduation.
‎你知道在她的Instagram ‎乱转是会被她看到的吧
You know she can see who's creeping around her Instagram, right?
‎-不知道 哦天啊 ‎-是的
-No. Oh, God. -Yep.
‎嘿 就算被说像复读机…
Hey, at the risk of sounding like a broken record--
‎我还没打开 别问了
I haven't opened it. Stop asking.
‎你不需要打开 它改变不了什么
You don't have to open it. It's not going to change anything.
‎这些突变意味着 ‎我有超过70%的机会会得癌症
These mutations mean that there's over a 70% chance that I'm gonna get cancer.
‎我母亲已经得了 那我几乎肯定会得
My mom already has it, so that makes it pretty damn certain.
‎理性地思考一下 你也不能这么肯定
Think about this rationally. You don't actually know that.
‎你是在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me right now?
‎如果结果是阳性 ‎那我就只有三种选择
If these results are positive, that means I have three options.
‎我可以等着得癌症
I can wait to get cancer,
‎割掉我的乳房或者摘除我的卵巢
chop off my boobs or remove my ovaries.
‎所以要么没孩子 要么没乳房 ‎要么都没有 真的是烂透了
So, no kids, or no boobs, or both. It's a really shitty situation.
‎抱歉 我没办法伪装成不要紧的样子
I'm sorry I'm not in the mood to make you feel better about it
‎来让你好受一点
by pretending like it's not.
‎-搞什么 ‎-在酒吧
-What the hell? -When you go to a bar,
‎如果有人对你做混蛋的事 ‎你就朝他的脸泼一杯酒
and somebody is an asshole to you, you throw a drink in their face.
‎-你真傻 ‎-没事吧
- You're an idiot. -Everything all right?
‎-有事 不过… ‎-我要走了
-No, but... -I'm gonna get going.
‎我要看片放松一下
I've got some Netflix and chilling I've been meaning to do.
‎-那位幸运的女伴是谁 ‎-看片还需要女伴
-Who's the lucky lady? -Is that what that means?
‎没有 就我自己 回头见
- Yeah, no, it's just me. I'll see you kids later.
‎-你想不想… ‎-好 我们走吧
- Do you wanna... -Yeah, let's go.
‎-肯尼先生 ‎-总统先生
-Mr. Kenny. -Mr. President.
‎告诉我 全国所有 ‎C4基金会的负责人都来了吗
Tell me, is the head of every C4 Foundation across the country here?
‎-你的吸引力可不小 ‎-我很乐意支持
-You're quite the draw. -Well, I'm glad to support.
‎这是不是意味着 你不会 ‎否决我们感兴趣的小小法案了
Does that mean you're not vetoing our little pet bill?
‎不 不是那个意思
No, that's not what it means.
‎想想C4基金为世界 ‎做出的美好贡献吧
Think about all the good that C4's are doing for the world.
‎我们要求的回报只是隐私而已
All we're asking for in return is privacy.
‎不 你们要求的 ‎是隐藏资金的花销目的
No, what you're asking for is to hide where you spend your money
‎这样你们就可以贿选而不必担心报复
so you can buy elections without fear of reprisal.
‎我们说的是 ‎帮助社区中最弱小的人群的
We're talking about social welfare organizations
‎社会福利组织
helping the most vulnerable in our communities,
‎-不是政治行动委员会 总统先生 ‎-好
-not Super PACs, Mr. President. -Okay.
‎我会认真考虑的
I'll take that under advisement.
‎-很高兴见到你 ‎-我也是
-Good to see you. -You, too.
莫斯谴责教师延长罢工后
‎集会爆发暴力事件
‎该死
Shit.
‎怎么了
So, what's going on?
‎我和伊莎贝尔为了件蠢事吵架了
I just had this stupid fight with Isabel.
‎我猜是源于压力 ‎副总统审查、订婚谣言…
It's the pressure, I guess. VP scrutiny, these engagement rumors...
‎突然之间 我们俩都被放在显微镜下
All of a sudden, we're both under the microscope.
‎一定很煎熬
That must be hard.
‎说到这个 还有别的事情引起了关注
Speaking of, though, something else came up under the lens. Um...
‎“马里卢斯圣地亚哥”这名字 ‎听起来熟悉吗
Does the name Mariluz Santiago sound familiar?
‎什么
What?
‎你的银行账单显示 ‎过去四年间你都在向她付款
Your bank statements show payments to her over the last four years,
‎我需要知道 ‎这事被挖出来时我要怎么回答
and I need to know what to say if it comes up.
‎她只是个老朋友
She's just an old friend.
‎是 但付款…
Right, but the payments...
‎我帮她付大学学费 ‎有什么大不了的
I helped her pay for college. What's the big deal?
‎你有什么瞒着我
What are you not telling me?
‎好吧
All right.
‎我16岁时 ‎去边境那边的华雷斯拜访我阿姨
When I was 16, I visited my aunt in Ju谩rez, just over the border,
‎她带我去了她教堂的集会
and she took me to this meeting at her church.
‎那里有很多孩子
And there were a lot of kids there.
‎结束后 她让我开车载其中一些孩子 ‎和我一起回德州的厄尔巴索
When it was over, she asked me to drive some of them back with me to El Paso.
‎我照做了
So I did.
‎几年后我才知道 ‎我阿姨搞的这个小团体
I learned a few years later that my aunt ran this group
‎把孩子们运离集团
that would take kids away from the cartels,
‎我开车接回来的孩子们没有证明材料
and the kids I drove back with me were undocumented.
‎你这是怎么过境的
How did you even get across?
‎那时候不一样
It was a different time back then.
‎那你一直付钱过去的女人…
So the woman that you've been paying--
‎是在我帮助下非法入境的人之一
She was someone I helped cross the border illegally.
‎还有谁知道这件事
Who else knows about this?
‎应该只有我、车上的孩子
As far as I can remember, it's just me, the kids in the car,
‎和我阿姨 她已经去世了
and my aunt. She passed away.
‎你不能告诉其他人 ‎这事只有我们俩知道 明白吗
You can't tell anybody else. This stays between you and I. Understood?
‎是 我明白
Yeah, I got it.
‎嘿…
- -Hey...
‎有我在
I got you.
‎好
Yeah.
‎-欢迎回家 ‎-怎么了
-Welcome home. -What is goin' on?
‎我们有一阵子 ‎没一起吃晚饭了 所以我想…
We haven't had dinner together in a while, so I thought...
‎别太兴奋了 只是餐厅打包的菜
Don't get too excited.  It's just takeout.
‎-你今天过得如何 ‎-正常
-How was your day? -Usual.
‎我给参议员帕克瑟尔的妻子 ‎苏珊打了电话
I called Susan, Senator Paxel's wife.
‎我想听听共和党关于罢工问题的态度
I wanted to get the Republican buzz on these walkouts.
‎-莫斯对结束罢工很上心 ‎-我们知道
-Moss is serious about strike-breaking. -We know.
‎我还给图书馆打了电话
I also called the library about maybe
‎考虑重新去他们的 ‎课后辅导活动当志愿者
volunteering for their after-school program again.
‎林 这是怎么回事
Lynn, what is this?
‎我在康复中心做了个决定
I made a decision in rehab.
‎我知道这件事 ‎对我们的影响 我想回到正轨
I know what this has done to us and I'm going to make it right.
‎你呢
Are you?
‎拿出来看吧 你没法忽视工作的
Go ahead. You can't ignore work.
我想要你
来过夜吧？
‎没事吧
Is everything all right?
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎-叙利亚的事 ‎-教师罢工
-Syria? -Teachers' strike?
‎国内外的暴力问题 我可以坐下吗
Violence at home and abroad. Mind if I sit?
‎我没看到哈珀 你呢
I don't see Harper around, do you?
‎喝威士忌吗
Scotch?
‎当然 有何不可谢谢
Sure. Why not? Thank you.
‎你状态如何
How you holding up through everything?
‎谈判不会有事的
The negotiations will be fine.
‎我只是不习惯 ‎每天都被质疑我是谁的问题
I'm just not used to having who I am questioned on a daily basis.
‎恐怕情况只会越来越糟
I'm afraid that's only gonna get worse.
‎归根结底 只要你知道自己是谁就好
At the end of the day, all that matters is that you know who you are.
‎-我听说莫斯集会的事了 ‎-所有人都在谴责抗议者
-I heard about the Moss rally. -Everyone's blaming the protesters.
‎他们是被打的人
They were the ones that got beat up.
‎莫斯说 在他的集会上 ‎出现恐怖行动是他们的错
Moss said it was their fault for terrorizing his rally.
‎什么时候支持教师的抗议活动 ‎成了恐怖行动了
Since when is protesting in support of teachers an act of terror?
‎从莫斯利用我们最卑鄙的本性开始
Since Moss started playing to our basest nature.
‎不管你信不信 这样可以拉到选票
Believe it or not, it actually gets votes.
‎-我们要怎么做 先生 ‎-我还不确定
-What are we gonna do, sir? -I'm not sure yet.
‎我只知道美国的劳工谈判历史
All I know is that the history of US labor negotiations
‎堆满了美国劳动者的尸体
is littered with the bodies of the American worker,
‎我要尽全力避免 ‎这种事情在我任上重演
and I have to do all I can to stop that from happening on my watch.
‎不幸的是 因为今天的暴力事件
Unfortunately, with the violence today,
‎州长们开始撤回原先的支持
the governors are pulling back their support.
‎我还担心 出现暴动只是时间问题
And I fear it's only a matter of time before we start having riots.
‎一切都是钱和权力的问题 对吗
It's always about money and power, isn't it?
‎我今晚出席的那场活动
The event I was at tonight,
‎那间房间里的人只要动动手指 ‎就能满足教师们的所有诉求
people in that room could single-handedly give the teachers everything they needed.
‎他们拥有的金钱数量真是离谱
It's obscene, the amount of money they have.
‎让老师们回到岗位上需要花费多少
How much would it cost to bring the teachers back to work?
‎三十亿美元
Three billion dollars.
‎加上我的签名同意
And my signature.
‎马上要到你的媒体活动了 兴奋吗
Excited about your press event?
‎是的 希望罗琳能信守承诺
Yup. Hopefully Lorraine keeps her promise.
青年主人组织
‎我看得出你没打算遵守你的承诺
I can see you're not planning on keeping yours.
‎这只是件T恤
It's just a T-shirt.
‎我只是想说 你要去的活动 ‎和青年主人组织没关系
I'm just saying this event you're going to has nothing to do with the Young Lords.
‎别这么高调
Just tone it down a bit.
‎你怎么能跟我说这种话
In what world was that the right thing to say to me?
‎我只是想说 别为了惹恼罗琳 ‎而在你做好事的时候
I'm just saying don't distract from the good you're doing
‎分散自己的注意力
to piss off Lorraine.
‎我该走了
I gotta go.
‎-做得好 哈珀 ‎-早上好 罗琳
-Nice work, Harper. -Good morning, Lorraine.
‎-你喜欢打乱我的日程表吗 ‎-什么意思
-Do you enjoy fucking up my schedule? -What do you mean?
‎这个亚伦不能跟我讲的 ‎破高层审查事项
This high-level clearance bullshit that Aaron can't tell me about
‎本该由他的代理人处理
that was supposed to be handled by his deputy
‎然而有人对此不满意
until someone got their panties in a twist about it,
‎结果我整个下午的安排都要取消
and now my entire afternoon is canceled.
‎只要亚伦还是总统的国家安全顾问
As long as Aaron is the president's national security advisor,
‎我就要求他做好本职工作 ‎而不是把任务委派出去
I expect him to do his job, not delegate it to a secondary player.
‎这口气就像个趾高气昂的办公室主任
Spoken like a glorified office manager.
‎以拍照机会为借口 ‎逃避工作的人可不是我
I'm not the one shirking my duty for photo ops.
‎什么情况 马斯
What is the matter, Marsy?
‎你想当副总统吗我很抱歉
Oh, did you wanna be VP? I'm so sorry.
‎竞选班子里不能再加上 ‎一个无聊的白人男子了
We couldn't have another boring white guy on the ticket.
‎你能自重吗 罗琳
Could you show some decorum, Lorraine?
‎我知道是怎么回事
I know what this is.
‎你在嫉妒 你的职业生涯走到头了
You are jealous. It's the end of your career.
‎在联邦政府工作39年
Thirty-nine years in the wheels of the federal bureaucracy
‎你有什么值得骄傲的政绩
and what do you have to show for it?
‎亚伦的政途刚起步 ‎就已经开始创造历史了
Aaron is just starting out and he's already making history.
‎青出于蓝
The student has surpassed the teacher,
‎而你还试图证明自己更厉害
and you're still trying to prove that your dick is bigger.
‎你猜怎么着你本来就不怎么样
Guess what? It never was.
希尔斯伯勒县
佛罗里达卫生部
‎有人以深肤色的人种为目标
Someone is targeting people with dark skin color?
‎看起来是这样
It looks that way.
‎怎么做到的没人记得被注射过
How? Nobody even remembers being injected.
‎我有个猜想
I have a theory.
‎这些是黑色素细胞 ‎把它们想象成色素工厂
These are melanocytes. Think of them as pigment factories.
‎这次的流感就是以它们为目标
This flu is designed to target them.
‎左边的细胞是健康人的
Now, the cells on the left are from healthy people.
‎-好吧 所以大家都病了 ‎-不 这要积少成多
-Okay, so everyone's sick. -No, it's a cumulative thing.
‎我们都有黑色素细胞 你有 我也有 ‎但我的有更多的色素制造器
We all have melanocytes. You, me. But mine have more pigment producers.
‎制造器越多 你的肤色就越深 ‎这种病毒也就会让你病得更厉害
The more you have, the darker you are, the sicker this thing makes you.
‎-这种病毒会不会是自然产生的 ‎-不可能
-Is there any way this is natural? -None.
‎不同种族的人在基因上几乎并无不同
There's virtually no genetic difference between people of different races,
‎差异少于百分之零点零四
less than 0.04%.
‎具有这般选择性的RNA病毒
There is no natural way an RNA virus that selective
‎在自然情况下不可能稳定到足以存活
could be stable enough to survive.
‎有人在利用 ‎这少于百分之零点零四的差异
Someone is exploiting a difference of less than 0.04%
‎来让特定人种生病
to make certain people sick?
‎马斯 我需要你去联络马克思肯尼
Mars, I need you to reach out to Max Kenny.
‎那个C4基金的人
The C4 Foundation guy?
‎你要让他和他基金会的人
Yeah, you're gonna get him and his foundation buddies
‎捐出三十亿美元给教师
to donate $3 billion earmarked for teachers.
‎-我能给的交换条件是什么 ‎-来自总统的感谢
-And what am I bringing to the table? -The gratitude of the president.
‎他们肯定要你保证不否决他们的法案
They're gonna want assurances that you're not vetoing their bill.
‎但我一定会否决他们的法案 ‎肯尼先生要清楚这一点
But I am vetoing their bill. Mr. Kenny needs to know that.
‎我想你已经有了足够支持否决的票数
I'm assuming you've got the votes to support the veto.
‎林的父亲在我还是个小助理时
The first thing that Lynn's father taught me to do
‎教我的第一件事就是 做好算数
when I was a lowly assistant was count.
‎是 我们有足够多否决法案的票数
Yes, we have what we need to kill the bill.
‎-我要你保证法案能通过 ‎-什么
-I need you to keep it alive. -Sorry?
‎当你压力太大时 ‎就把紧绷的弦松一松
Wherever you're pressured, release the screws.
‎你要我确保 ‎法案在否决投票后仍能通过
You want me to make sure that the bill survives the veto?
‎虽然看上去并非如此 ‎但我觉得这是个很好的交易
It may not seem like it now, sir, but I think it's a very good trade.
‎我们仅仅在制作环节 ‎就雇佣了32位女性
We're employing 32 women in manufacturing alone.
‎政府拨给这个项目的一万美元
And the government will get back the $10,000 it granted to the project,
‎两年内就能赚回来 对比一下…
within two years. Compare that--
‎-那是亚伦吗 ‎-亚伦萧来了
- Aaron Shore is here.
‎你来干什么
What are you doing here?
‎我昨天把这事加入日程 ‎好确保媒体会露面
I added it to my schedule yesterday just to make sure the press would show up.
‎真抱歉打断大家 帕尔多小姐请继续
I'm so sorry to interrupt. Ms. Pardo, please.
‎你穿的外套是 ‎赋权计划的原创款式吗
Is the coat you're wearing an Empowerment Plan original?
‎是啊
Indeed it is.
‎愿意展示一下吗
Care to demonstrate?
‎运动风格 功能实用
Sporty, functional.
‎可以变成睡袋 还能做救生工具
It converts into a sleeping bag and is life-saving.
‎真的很棒 伊莎
That's a really great job, Isi.
‎我真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
‎你妈妈会为你骄傲的
Your mother would be proud.
‎打扰一下 萧先生
Excuse me, Mr. Shore?
‎你确定吗
You're certain of this?
‎凭直觉 我重新检查了 ‎我们鸟类朋友的样本
On a hunch, I re-checked the samples from our bird friends
‎发现了一套类似的定向色素的机制
and discovered a similar pigment-targeting mechanism.
‎所以它才只感染红色的鸟
Why it was only targeting red birds.
‎你了解优生学吗
Are you familiar with eugenics?
‎知道 希特勒 德国纳粹
Yeah. Hitler, Nazi Germany.
‎还有长岛 ‎一个美国医生 查尔斯达文波特
And Long Island. And an American doctor, Charles Davenport.
‎他研究遗传学 结论非常有害
He studied heredity, badly.
‎他是推广种族基因优越性的
He's the father of a scientific movement that promoted the idea
‎科学运动之父 当时非常受追捧
of racial genetic superiority, very popular at the time.
‎追随者包括麦迪逊格兰特 ‎和约翰克罗格博士…
Fans included Madison Grant and Dr. John Kellogg--
‎-那个推广玉米片早餐的人 ‎-是的
-The cornflakes guy? -Yes.
‎还有希特勒 ‎他以达文波特的成果为蓝本
And Hitler, who used Davenport's work as a blueprint.
‎-这可不是我们引以为傲的文化输出 ‎-但影响却相当深远
-Not our proudest export. -But one of our more enduring.
‎-例如种族隔离 南非 ‎-海岸线计划 生化武器计划
-Take apartheid, South Africa. -Project Coast, the bioweapons program?
‎是的 我被派去了 ‎监管海岸线计划的那个团队
Yes. I was assigned to the team to monitor Project Coast.
‎他们在研究寻找通过基因定向感染
They were researching ways to genetically target black South Africans
‎南非黑人的致命疾病
with lethal diseases.
‎-他们成功了吗 ‎-没有 谢天谢地
-Did they succeed? -No, thank God.
‎但他们的成果 正如达文波特的一样 ‎仍在激励新的研究
But their work, like Davenport's, continues to inspire.
‎-抱歉 迎新活动拖太晚了 ‎-你来了
- Sorry, orientation ran late. -There she is.
‎别担心 孩子
Don't worry about it, kiddo.
‎-迎新 ‎-是的 我在带一群新生
-Uh, orientation? -Yeah, I'm leading a group of freshmen.
‎嘿 真不错
Hey, that's great.
‎我知道你生日刚过 所以…
Oh. Um, I know it was just your birthday, so...
‎你不必破费的
Oh, you didn't have to.
‎我知道 但我想送给你
I know, but I wanted to.
‎如果你打开它…
If you open it...
‎他们是我的亲生父母
Those are my biological parents.
‎我是被收养的 所以我从不认识他们
I was adopted, so I never knew them.
‎我的父母 我真正的父母
And my parents, my real parents,
‎我的养父母 总之 他们很好 但…
my adopted parents, whatever, they're great, but...
‎我觉得能知道 ‎自己的血脉从哪来 挺好的
I thought it's good to know where we come from.
‎是啊
Yeah.
‎戴上看看
Try it on.
‎我还想着可以带你去音乐会
I also thought I could take you to a concert.
‎这好像是挺适合21岁做的事
That seems like a good 21-year-old thing to do.
‎是啊 真棒 赛斯 谢谢
Um, yeah. That's great, Seth. Thanks.
‎对不起 我其实明天要早起
I'm sorry, I actually have an early morning.
‎饮料钱我该付多少给你
So, um, what do I owe you for the drink?
‎不用 别担心 下回你请
Oh. No, don't worry about it. You can just get the next one.
‎好吧
All right.
‎那就下次见
I guess I'll see ya.
‎-好的 ‎-好的
-Okay. -Okay.
‎-再见 ‎-再见
-Bye. -Bye.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎我听说老师们回去上班了
I hear the teachers are going back to work.
‎暂时解决 等我当选后 ‎我们可以做点真正的好事
Temporary fix. Once I'm elected, we can do some real good.
‎这样的改变挺好的
That'll be a nice change.
‎你说什么
Excuse me?
‎你说过不会拿他们的钱的
You said you weren't gonna take their money.
‎但我猜如果罗琳觉得没问题…
But I guess if Lorraine thinks it's okay--
‎-不是她的主意 ‎-那就更糟了
-It wasn't her idea. -That's worse.
‎你要我怎么办坐以待毙吗
What the hell do you expect me to do? Sit here and do nothing?
‎你拿了黑钱
You took dark money.
‎-是为了老师们不是为了我的竞选 ‎-这次是这样而已
For teachers! Not for my campaign. -This time. -
‎总统先生 刚从国会山得到消息
Mr. President, just got back from the Hill.
‎-没问题了 ‎-谢谢
-You're good to go ahead. - Thank you.
‎什么情况
What the hell's going on?
‎你跟罗琳吵架 ‎跟我吵架 有什么问题吗
You're picking fights with Lorraine, with me. Have we got a problem?
‎你让我来不是为了对你言听计从的
You didn't ask me here to be your yes-man.
‎至少告诉我 你还会否决非公开法案
At least tell me you're still vetoing the non-disclosure bill.
‎-你跟我说过你会否决的 ‎-是的 我会否决
-You told me you would veto that. -Yes, I'm going to veto it!
‎你当然会了
Of course you are.
‎哈珀已经和国会山确认过
Now that Harper's checked with the Hill
‎他们有足够票数令你的否决无效
to make sure they have the votes to override you.
‎天啊 这…
Man, that's...
‎真是绝妙的政治手腕
that's really great politics.
‎你知道吗 艾米丽 ‎今天太漫长了 晚安吧
You know what, Emily? It's been a long day. Good night.
‎该死 这很有必要
Damn, that was necessary.
‎没错
Truth.
‎-听起来你今天过得很充实 ‎-是的 我拍了些东西
-Sounds like you had a day. -Yeah, I just filmed some stuff.
‎你和总统探讨了教育政策
You talked education policy with the president.
‎你影响了他的决策
You affected his decisions.
‎这可真性感
-Now that is some sexy ass shit. -
‎-好 ‎-不
- Okay. -Nope.
‎-我要去尿尿 ‎-我还没亲够你呢
- -Uh-uh. -I gotta pee. -I'm not done kissing you yet.
‎干 你疯了
- -Fuck, you're crazy.
‎我喜欢你
I like you.
‎你不了解我
You don't know me.
‎美国特勤局了解的事会让你吃惊的
You'd be surprised at what the US Secret Service knows.
‎这算是…
Is this gonna be like a...
‎这算是工作需要吗
Is this gonna be a thing at work?
‎当然是的
Oh, definitely.
‎不过说真的 你…
For real, though, you...
‎你很聪明
You're smart.
‎也很性感
And you're sexy.
‎除此之外我还需要知道什么呢
What more do I need to know?
结果：阴性
‎我今天在国会山 ‎做了些老套的艰难交易
I did some old-fashion horse-trading on the Hill today.
‎-你一直都是那个调停斡旋的角色 ‎-我感觉回到了年轻时代
- You always were a fixer. -I felt young again.
‎让我想起自己是擅长自己的工作的
Reminded me that I'm good at my job.
‎-这一点还用质疑吗 ‎-罗琳今天说了些话
- Was that ever in question? -Lorraine said something today.
‎-说我嫉妒亚伦 ‎-这很正常
-That I'm jealous of Aaron. -It's only natural.
‎他和柯克曼合作无间 接触频繁 ‎他以前做的是你的工作
He worked so closely with Kirkman, all that access. He used to have your job.
‎-我不嫉妒亚伦 ‎-当然了
-I'm not jealous of Aaron. -Of course not.
‎这一届政府对你来说 ‎是绝佳的晚年岗位
This administration's a great third act for you.
‎如果他当选我想一直做下去
I'm gonna wanna stay on if he gets elected.
‎你不想开始写 ‎那本你一直想写的书吗
Don't you want to get started on that book you always wanted to write?
‎你说过我是个好编辑 ‎我们可以一起写
You said I was a good editor. We could work on it together.
‎到时候看吧
We'll see.
‎谢谢你今天来
Thank you for coming today.
‎我会一直支持你的 你知道的
Well, I'll always be there for you. You know that.
‎你什么时候改的名
When did you change your name?
‎我说过了 我父母在…
I already told you, my parents changed it--
‎你上幼儿园之前改的 ‎因为他们想让你融入集体
Before you started kindergarten 'cause they wanted you to assimilate.
‎那你六年级的照片上 ‎为什么写着亚伦里维拉
Why are you listed as Aaron Rivera in your sixth grade class photo, then?
‎我在高中时改的
I changed it in high school.
‎那你之前跟我撒谎了
So you lied to me?
‎我没有撒谎 只是不想细说
I didn't lie to you. I didn't want to get into it.
‎你最好还是细说一下
Well, you better get into it.
‎记得我去的那个预备学校吗
You remember that prep school I went to?
‎记得 全奖 毕业典礼发言学生代表 ‎到现在还写在你的简历上
Yeah, full scholarship, valedictorian. It's still on your r茅sum茅.
‎我是年级里唯一的拉丁裔
I was the only Latino in my grade.
‎我的同学以为我 ‎是靠足球奖学金进来的
My classmates thought that I got in on a soccer scholarship.
‎他们还跟我说老师给我打分会松一些
They also told me that teachers would grade me easier
‎因为他们以为我的母语不是英语
because they thought English was my second language.
‎明明就是啊 天啊
Which it wasn't. Christ.
‎我记得有一次德州历史大考
I remember this big Texas history test.
‎我得了最高分
And I scored the highest.
‎老师说 这是因为我是圣安娜的后裔
And the teacher said it was because I was a descendant of Santa Anna.
‎“要记得阿拉莫之战 孩子们
"And remember the Alamo, kids.
‎不能总是让里维拉先生胜过你们”
You can't keep letting Mr. Rivera beat you."
‎这种情况的错处在于
You know what's wrong about it is,
‎他们说这些话并非恶意 ‎而是真的相信这些狗屁观点
they're not just saying that to be mean. They actually believe that shit.
‎所以到申请大学的时候 我改了名字
So when it came time to apply for college, I changed my name
‎就不会有更多猜疑
so there wouldn't be any more doubts,
‎没人会说我录取是因为…你知道的…
so nobody could say I got in just because... You know...
‎我上的是耶鲁 混蛋
I went to Yale, cabr贸n.
‎那些破事我每天都要面对
I had to deal with shit like that every day of my life.
‎“你英语说得真好 你好有异域风情
"Oh, you speak such good English. Oh, you're so exotic.
‎你在波多黎各人里算聪明的”
Oh, you're so smart for a Puerto Rican."
‎-那你该明白啊 ‎-不明白
-Well, you get it, then. -No!
本集中所用到的真人采访画面都由纪录片影人提供
他们的观点没有剧本支持 均为个人观点
视频剪辑标准为内容和时长
‎蠢人永远会说蠢话
Stupid people are going to say stupid shit
‎不管我们为他们如何委屈自己
no matter how much of ourselves we amputate for them.
‎他们永远能找到理由看不起你
They're always gonna find a reason to look down on you.
‎我想凭借才华而受到赏识 ‎我不会为此道歉的
I'm not gonna apologize for wanting to be judged on my own merits.
‎拜托别跟我扯那套精英的屁话
Oh, please! Don't give me that meritocracy bullshit.
‎看看你自己 ‎一副欧洲人的好面孔 白皮肤
Look at yourself. The European good looks, the light skin.
‎你以为这些都没帮上忙吗
You think that shit didn't help you?
‎你希望我在白宫跑来跑去
You want me to march around the White House
‎穿着背后印着青年主人组织的T恤 ‎和总统吵架吗
with a Young Lords T-shirt on my back, picking fights with the president?
‎我做这份工作 ‎不能去当活动家 伊莎
I don't get to be an activist in this job, Isi.
‎在这事上我已经给足了耐心 ‎但这是基本的原则问题
I've tried to be so patient with this, but that is some basic bullshit.
‎-你这是选择假装白人… ‎-我没有
-You chose to pass-- -I don't pass.
‎有 你就是这样做的
Yes, yes, you really do.
‎好吗我又不傻 ‎我知道自己长什么样
Okay? And I'm not stupid. I know what I look like.
‎我也能照你的方式做
And I could have done what you did.
‎-但我选择了不去在意 ‎-好吧
-But I chose not to give a fuck. - Okay.
‎对不起 我为你的经历 ‎感到难过 真的
I'm sorry. I feel bad for what you went through, I really do.
‎但我们其他人都要面对那些事 ‎甚至更糟的事
But the rest of us have been dealing with that shit and worse.
‎这要怪你
Well, it's on you.
‎我不知道哪件事更糟心 亚伦
I don't know what bothers me more, Aaron.
‎是你撒谎 还是你是个懦夫
The fact that you're a liar or that you're a coward.
‎妈妈 我刚想跟你视频通话
Mom, I just tried to FaceTime you.
‎我想我现在不能连互联网
I guess I must not be connected to the Internet right now.
‎我拿到结果了 我没事
Um... I got the results. I'm okay.
‎谢天谢地 我好害怕会遗传给你
Thank God. I was so scared I gave this to you.
‎你没事吧
Are you okay?
‎-我没事 ‎-妈妈 真的 你感觉如何
- I'm fine. -Mom, really, how are you?
‎你知道我讨厌这个问题
You know I hate that question.
‎如果你能够信任我 ‎让我和你的医生们聊的话
Maybe if you trusted me to talk to your doctors,
‎我就不会问了
I wouldn't have to ask.
‎艾米丽 不是我不信任你
Oh, Em, it's not that I don't trust you.
‎我有别的安排
I just have other plans.
‎柯克曼的副总统人选 亚伦萧 ‎今天和墨西哥裔美国退伍士兵对话
Kirkman's VP pick, Aaron Shore, spoke to Mexican American veterans today,
‎过去一周他参加了很多竞选活动
after a long week of campaigning.
‎有很多人在说 ‎我是个具有历史意义的候选人
There's been a lot of talk about me as an historic candidate,
‎我对此表示感谢 我肩上担负的过去
and I appreciate what that means, the legacy that I carry on my shoulders.
‎但我不是这次选举中 ‎唯一一个在创造历史的人
But I'm not the only one making history in this election.
‎在过去几年间 ‎我有机会和柯克曼总统并肩工作
Over the past years, I've gotten to work closely with President Kirkman.
‎私下也有往来
I've gotten to know him personally.
‎我很荣幸 ‎他既是我的导师 也是朋友
And I'm proud to call him a mentor and a friend.
‎要说哪个候选人 ‎具有历史意义 那就是他
And if there ever was an historic candidate, it's him.
‎投票给他就是我们创造历史的机会
And voting for him is our chance to make history.
‎我父亲以前是个合同工
My dad was a contractor.
‎我记得有时到周末 ‎他会带我去建筑工地
I remember sometimes on the weekends, he would take me to his construction site.
‎我们俩就坐在那
The two of us would just sit there,
‎盯着还未完工的
staring up at these giant iron and steel skeletons of buildings
‎巨大的钢铁建筑骨架
that hadn't been finished.
‎我经常想象住在这些建筑里的人
Often, I would think about the people who'd live in those buildings,
‎以及他们会在建筑里做的事
and how those buildings would serve them.
‎从很多意义上讲 ‎这就是我现在看待美国的方式
In many ways, it's how I see America today.
‎我们能采用前辈留下的骨架
Can we take the skeleton that the forefathers left us,
‎让这个国家服务所有人 ‎而不是少部分人吗
and make a country that serves everyone, not just a select few?
‎这是个好问题
That's a good question.
‎我有各种想法
I have ideas.
‎如果我们能在这些想法的基础上 ‎进行建造 而非破坏
And if we can build on those ideas instead of tear them down,
‎我相信我们可以打造出美好的未来
I believe that we can make something beautiful.
‎大家一起 所有人
Together. All of us.
汤姆柯克曼 竞选总统
‎天啊 我都会投票给你
Hell, I'd vote for you.
‎做得好 当蒂 抓住了宏观要点
Terrific job, Dontae. Captures the big picture.
‎总统先生 能见一下您吗
Mr. President, could I see you for a minute?
‎马斯 你刚错过了一条精彩的广告 ‎我们也许能赢
Mars, you just missed an amazing ad. We might win this thing.
‎这东西今早出现在网上
This came in over the Internet this morning.
‎我觉得您应该看一下
Something I think you need to see.
亚历克斯柯克曼去世
‎是意外车祸还是总统谋杀？
柯克曼总统
‎是否导演了妻子的死亡？
‎天啊 这是什么
Oh, my God. What is this?
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177